export const Data = [
    {id:1, index:1, sortKey:"easy", problemDescription:"Find for X:"   ,mathProblem:"7x - 6 = 22", trueAnswer:4},
    {id:2, index:2, sortKey:"easy",problemDescription:"Find for X:" ,mathProblem:"5 + 2x = 15", trueAnswer:1},
    {id:3, index:3, sortKey:"easy",problemDescription:"Find for X:" ,mathProblem:"4x + 3 = 11", trueAnswer:1},
    {id:4, index:4,  sortKey:"easy",problemDescription:"Find for X:" ,mathProblem:"-5x + 20 = 25", trueAnswer:1},
    {id:5, index:5,  sortKey:"easy",problemDescription:"Find for X:" ,mathProblem:"12x + 0 = 144", trueAnswer:1},
    {id:6, index:6,  sortKey:"easy",problemDescription:"Find for X:" ,mathProblem:"-10x - 19 = 19 - 8x ", trueAnswer:1},

    {id:11, index:1, sortKey:"medium",problemDescription:"Evaluate, when X = 10:" ,mathProblem:" 30 - |-x + 6|", trueAnswer:26 },
    {id:12, index:2,  sortKey:"medium",problemDescription:"Evaluate when X = 2 and Y = -2:" ,mathProblem:"2xy^3 + x - 2y", trueAnswer:1},
    {id:13, index:3,  sortKey:"medium",problemDescription:"How many solutions does the equation 2x2 + 3x = 8 have?" ,mathProblem:"", trueAnswer:2},
    {id:14, index:4,  sortKey:"medium",problemDescription:"Evaluate:" ,mathProblem:"11+\\sqrt{-4 + 6ร4รท3}", truetrueAnswer:13},
    {id:15, index:5,  sortKey:"medium",problemDescription:"Solve the equation:" ,mathProblem:"-0.25 x + 1.3 = -0.55 x - 0.2", truetrueAnswer:-5},
    {id:16, index:6,  sortKey:"medium",problemDescription:"What is the slope of a line perpendicular to the line x = -3?" ,mathProblem:"", trueAnswer:0},

    {id:21, index:1, sortKey:"hard",problemDescription:"What is the number of solutions of this eequation? (The Answer should be a number)" ,mathProblem:"(x^2 + 1)^2 + 2(x^2 + 1) - 3 = 0", trueAnswer:1},
    {id:22, index:2,  sortKey:"hard",problemDescription:"For all x real:" ,mathProblem:"\\sqrt{(x^2 -4x + 4)}", trueAnswer:"|x-2|"},
    {id:23, index:3,  sortKey:"hard",problemDescription:"" ,mathProblem:"\\sqrt{(x 2 + 6x + 9)} =", trueAnswer:"|x+3|"},
    {id:24, index:4,  sortKey:"hard",problemDescription:"Solve the equation:" ,mathProblem:"2 (4^{x+1}) = 4 (8^{x+2})", trueAnswer:-5},
    {id:25, index:5,  sortKey:"hard",problemDescription:"How many solutions do the equation have? (The truetrueAnswer should be a number)" ,mathProblem:"1/x + 1/(x + 1) = 1/3", trueAnswer:2},
    {id:26, index:6,  sortKey:"hard",problemDescription:"Simplify:" ,mathProblem:"9\\log _9(4)", trueAnswer:4}
]